[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The French Foreign Legion was formed in 1831 to conquer which nation ?", "correct_answer": "Algeria", "incorrect_answers": ["Morocco", "Tunisia", "Vietnam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What toy did Apollo 8 astronauts carry into space in 1968?", "correct_answer": "Silly Putty", "incorrect_answers": ["Yo-Yo", "Rubiks Cube", "Lincoln Logs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does sagination mean?", "correct_answer": "The act of fattening up", "incorrect_answers": ["The state of being pale", "The state of being morose", "The act of bleeding"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Cadmium?", "correct_answer": "Cd", "incorrect_answers": ["Cm", "C", "Ca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A large exposition at the Royal Observatory, Greenwich is devoted to horology, a science that studies what?", "correct_answer": "time", "incorrect_answers": ["navigation", "lenses", "comets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is NOT a course served at the banquet in which Indiana Jones and company take part in Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom?", "correct_answer": "Elephant tail shish-cabob", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye Ball Soup", "Chilled Monkey Brains", "Snake Suprise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which artificial island is situated in San Francisco Bay, between San Francisco and Oakland?", "correct_answer": "Treasure Island", "incorrect_answers": ["Hulhumal\u00e9", "Port Island", "Flakfortet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By 2004, how many people had been outside Earths atmosphere?", "correct_answer": "About 400", "incorrect_answers": ["About 100", "About 200", "About 300"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "8 is the square root of 64.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie Blazing Saddles released?", "correct_answer": "1974", "incorrect_answers": ["1972", "1982", "1978"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ruth Lanier (Rick Chances informant) has a line in the film where she talks about the stars. Basically, she says that the stars:", "correct_answer": "are the eyes of God.", "incorrect_answers": ["are the windows to the soul.", "havent been visible lately, due to the presence of the smog/marine layer.", "never shine so bright as when were guilty."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Aristocats, the butler is so scared of the dogs that he runs away leaving some items behind him. Which of the following did he not leave behind?", "correct_answer": "His overcoat", "incorrect_answers": ["His umbrella", "His hat", "His motorcycle sidecar"]}]